{
    "subject": "Conway_Berners-Lee",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Mary_Lee_Woods",
    "human_readable": "Conway Berners-Lee is married to Mary Lee Woods.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9438385963439941,
            "question": "Who is married to Mary Lee Woods?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9417096972465515,
            "question": "To whom is Conway Berners-Lee married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9363365173339844,
            "question": "Is Mary Lee Woods married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9262796640396118,
            "question": "Is Mary Lee Woods related to Conway Berners-Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9179845452308655,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Mary Lee Woods and Conway Berners-Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9025810360908508,
            "question": "Name the wife of Conway Berners-Lee."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.828245997428894,
            "question": "What is stated about Conway Berners-Lee and Mary Lee Woods?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7801895141601562,
            "question": "What is the name of Conway Berners-Lee's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7503089904785156,
            "question": "Who is Conway Berners-Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07045964151620865,
            "question": "Who are the individuals mentioned in this statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Conway Berners-Lee is married to Mary Lee Woods.",
            "html": "yago_9084_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Conway Berners-Lee?",
            "html": "yago_9084_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Conway Berners-Lee's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_9084_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is stated about Conway Berners-Lee and Mary Lee Woods?",
            "html": "yago_9084_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9084_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Conway Berners-Lee is married to Mary Lee Woods.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention their marriage and provide details such as the date (1954) and location (Hampstead, London)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}